Bre
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/3Z2/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Cat
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/DM1/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Daelisse
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/N7U/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Daniel
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/YQX/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Derin
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/CWA/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Ember P.
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/QEL/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Ember S.
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/I7A/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Hannah
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/MGN/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Hens
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/WEC/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Liam
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/22I/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Patrick
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/57D/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Sam
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/1DA/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Simon
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/RML/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


Zeke
Hey, here is your link for the holiday party: <https://dgholiday.liambloom.dev/B5H/ticket>. You should print this ticket out (using the download button in the top right) or write coal/candy cane and put it on the gift


